morevisibility.com 2015-12-06

# MoreVisibility's Privacy Policy

This is the web site of MoreVisibility, Inc.

Our postal address is  
925 So Federal Highway, Ste 750  
Boca Raton, FL 33432

We can be reached via e-mail at info@MoreVisibility.com or you can reach us by telephone at 561.620.9682

###  1\. Information Collection

We collect information from you in several different ways on this Site. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. For example, we can use your personal information to:

  * Help make the Site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once
  * Help you quickly find information, products, and services
  * Help us create content that is most relevant to you
  * Alert you to new information, products, and services that we offer

**A)   **Cookies and Other Technology. Like many sites, the Site employs cookies and web beacons (also known as clear GIF technology or "action tags") to speed your navigation of the Site, recognize you and your access privileges, and track your Site usage.

(i)  Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored as text files by your Internet browser on your computer’s hard drive. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from web sites or to remove cookies from your hard drive, but if you do, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Site. We have to use cookies to enable you to select products, place them in an online shopping cart, and to purchase those products. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. THE SITE’S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER’S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER’S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION. Our cookies are not "spyware".

(ii)  Web beacons assist in delivering cookies and help us determine whether a web page on the Site has been viewed and, if so, how many times. For example, any electronic image on the Site, such as an ad banner, can function as a web beacon.

(iii)  We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor site content to users or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are requested). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us. In certain instances, we will use this information to market to you on other websites, in an effort of re-engaging your interest on us and/or specific services of ours, through specialized targeting, referred to as Remarketing or Retargeting.

(iv)  As an example, Google collects certain information via cookies and web beacons to determine which web pages are visited or what products are requested. Please note that any information collected by Google via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any customer's personal information collected by us. Visitors can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

(v)  Log Files. As is true of most web sites, the Site server automatically recognizes the Internet URL from which you access the Site. We may also log your Internet protocol ("IP") address, Internet service provider, and date/time stamp for system administration, order verification, internal marketing, and system troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address may indicate the location of your computer on the Internet.)

**B)**   MoreVisibility uses [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/analytics/), and is a [Google Analytics Authorized Partner](http://www.google.com/analytics/partners.html). Google Analytics uses four first-party cookies that are set on a visitor’s computer which allow anonymous web site usage data to be collected. MoreVisibility uses this anonymous information to study and observe how our web site is performing, and how we can improve the user-experience of our web site. MoreVisibility does not in any way, shape, or form re-distribute, re-sell, or make publicly available the anonymous web site data that we collect. The first-party cookies set on your computer by our web site are 128-bit secure socket layer (SSL) encrypted, and can only be read by our primary domain.

###  2.  Use of Your Information

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information which you requested.

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line or following up to information requested from us.

If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them. Consumers can access this information by e-mail us at the above address.

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Consumers can have this information corrected by sending us e-mail at the above address.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server and will notify visitors through a pop-up screen on our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.

Read Less »
